A Guide to the American Conservation Association (ACA) records FA475
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Files, 1
  - Grant Files, 2001; 1.12
    - The Trust for Public Land and Report (Box 98)
    - The Wildlife Conservation Society (Box 98)
    - The Wilderness Society (Box 98)
    - World Resources Institute (Box 98)
    - World Wildlife Fund Conservation Foundation (Box 98)
    - Appalachian Mountain Club (Box 98)
    - Conservation Law Foundation (Box 98)
    - Friends of Earth and Trustee for Alaska (Box 98)
  - Grant Files, 2001-2002; 1.13
    - American Land Trust, 2001 (Box 104)
    - Adirondack Council/Alaska Conservation Foundation, 2002 (Box 104)
    - American Rivers, 2002 (Box 104)
    - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development Coast Alliance, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Coast Alliance, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Conservation Fund, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Conservation International, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Conservation Law Foundation, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Earth Day Network, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Earth Justice Legal Defense Fund, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Endangered Species Coalition, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Environmental Advocates, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Friends of the Earth, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Green Guide Institute, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Lady Bird Johnson Wildflower Center, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Land Trust Alliance, 2002 (Box 104)
    - LCV Education Fund, 2002 (Box 104)
    - National Audubon Society, 2002 (Box 104)
    - National Parks and Conservation Association, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, 2002 (Box 104)
    - New York Conservation Education Fund, 2002 (Box 104)
    - New York Parks and Conservation, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Open Space Institute, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Partnership Community Project, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Project for Public Spaces, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Rachel's Network, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Rails to Trails, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Rep Environmental Educational Foundation, 2002; 2 folders. (Box 104)
    - River Watch Network, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Scenic America, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Scenic Hudson, 2002 (Box 104)
    - SE Alaska Conservation Council, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Trust for Public Land, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Wilderness Society, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Wildlife Conservation Society, 2002 (Box 104)
    - World Resources Institute, 2002 (Box 104)
    - WWF Conservation Foundation, 2002 (Box 104)
    - Yale School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2002 (Box 104)
  - Grant Files, 2003; 1.14
    - A-Z, 2003 (Box 117)
  - Grant Files, 2004; 1.15
    - Alaska Conservation Foundation, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Appalachlan Mountain Club, 2004 (Box 107)
    - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Center for International Environmental Law, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Coast Alliance, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Conservation Fund, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Conservation International, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Conservation Law Foundation, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Lady Bird Johnson Wildflower Center, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Land Trust Alliance, 2004 (Box 107)
    - League of Conservation Voters Education Fund, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Maine Coast Heritage Trust, 2004 (Box 107)
    - National Audubon Society, 2004 (Box 107)
    - National Parks and Conservation Association, 2004 (Box 107)
    - National Wildlife Federation, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, 2004 (Box 107)
    - New York League of Conservation Voters, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Open Space Institute, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Parks and Trails New York, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Project for Public Spaces, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Rails-to-Trails, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Rep. Environmental Educational Foundation, 2004 (Box 107)
    - River Watch Network, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Scenic America, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Scenic Hudson, Inc., 2004 (Box 107)
    - SE Alaska Conservation Council, 2004 (Box 107)
    - The Trust for Public Land, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Wilderness Society, 2004 (Box 107)
    - Wildlife Conservation Society, 2004 (Box 107)
    - World Resources Institute, 2004 (Box 107)
    - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), 2004 (Box 107)
- Organization, 1964-1971; 2
  - American Express Company (Box 14)
  - Annual Reports - Printing Proof (Box 14)
  - Audits (Box 14)
  - Annual Report of Treasurer (Box 14)
  - Annual Statutory Report (Box 14)
  - Board of Directors (Box 14)
  - Booklet (Box 14)
  - By-Laws (Box 14)
  - Clippings (Box 14)
  - Charter (Box 14)
  - Organization (Box 14)
  - Consultants (Box 14)
  - District of Columbia Licensing and Filing Requirements (Box 14)
  - Employees (Box 14)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of New York (Box 14)
  - Finance - Custody Account (Box 14)
  - Finance - Gifts (Box 14)
  - Finance - Investments (Box 14)
  - Insurance (Box 14)
  - Insurance - Employees (Box 14)
  - Legal (Box 14)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1963 (Box 14)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1961 (Box 14)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1960 (Box 14)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1959 (Box 14)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1971 (Box 15)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1968 (Box 15)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1967 (Box 15)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1966 (Box 15)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Office Equipment (Box 15)
  - Office Matters (Box 15)
  - Office Space - Lease (Box 15)
  - Office Space - State Council of Parks Office Space (Box 15)
  - Plan and Purpose (Box 15)
  - Press Releases (Box 15)
  - Organization - Reports Employee's Identification Number (Box 15)
  - Organization - Reports Employer - Management Improper Practices Act (Box 15)
  - Organization - Reports New York (State of) Department of Labor (NY Minimum Wage Act) (Box 15)
  - Organization - Special Fund (Box 15)
  - Organization - Subscriptions and Book Purchases (Box 15)
  - Organizaiton - Taxes (Box 15)
  - Organization - Taxes - Application For Tax Exemption (Box 15)
  - Organization - Taxes - New York City - New York State Income Tax Bureau (Box 15)
  - Organization - Taxes - Social Security (Box 15)
- Administration, 3
  - ACA Minutes, 1958-1966 (Box 20)
  - ACA Minutes/Meetings - Executive Committee (Box 20)
  - Annual Meeting - General, 1958-1965; 5 folders. (Box 20)
  - ACA- Meetings - Kenneth Chorley (Box 20)
  - ACA Form 990-A Federal Tax Report 1959-1969 inclusive (Box 57)
  - Form 990-A and Form 990-AR, 1959-1974 (Box 57)
  - New York State - Form NYCF-2 - Annual Report of Charitable Organization, 1967-1970 inclusive (Box 57)
  - Meeting Agendas, 1959-1975; Folder for each year. (Box 58)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JHPI) (Box 59)
  - Grants to ACA and JHPI, 1969-1978 (Box 59)
  - CORC Report Minutes, 1962-1964 (Box 59)
  - Man and His Urban Environment - Informational Material, Press Release, Comments, Promotional Letters, etc. (Box 59)
  - The Electric Utility Industry and the Environment - Report to the Citizens Advisory Committee on Recreation and Natural Beauty by the Electric Utility Industry Task Force on Environment, 1968 (Box 59)
  - Jackson Airport Study, 1975; 1978 (Box 59)
  - CACEQ - Publications (Box 59)
  - CACEQ - Annual Reports, 1967-1975 (Box 59)
  - Board Meetings ACA/JHPI - Colonial Williamsburg, 1984 October 22-23 (Box 80)
  - Board Meetings ACA/JHPI - Jackson, Wyoming, 1985 September 4-5 (Box 80)
  - Board Meetings ACA/JHPI - Montgomery Place, 1986 October 2-3 (Box 80)
  - Board Meetings ACA/JHPI - Jackson, Wyoming, 1987 September 1-4 (Box 80)
  - Board Meetings ACA/JHPI - Imperatore yacht and Montgomery Place, 1988 October 12-14 (Box 80)
  - Board Meetings ACA/JHPI - Adirondacks, 1989 September 25-28 (Box 80)
  - Board Meetings ACA/JHPI - Jackson, Wyoming, 1990 September 6-7 (Box 80)
  - Board Meetings ACA/JHPI - Mohonk, New Paltz, 1991 October 9-11 (Box 81)
  - Board Meetings ACA/JHPI - Jackson Wyoming, 1992 September 10-11 (Box 81)
  - Board Meetings ACA/JHPI - Woodstock, Vermont, 1993 October 21 (Box 81)
  - Board Meetings ACA - Central Park Zoo, New York, 1994 September 22 (Box 81)
  - Board Meetings ACA - Hudson River Museum- Yonkers, New York, 1995 September 21 (Box 81)
  - Board Meetings - Old Miscellaneous information (Box 81)
  - ACA 40th Anniversary, 1999 (Box 96)
  - C&F Photos for ACA, 1999 (Box 96)
  - ACA 40th Anniversary Report, 1999 November (Box 96)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1974-1998 (Box 101)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1974-1998 (Box 102)
  - Draper Associates (Box 103)
  - ACA - Agendas of Board Meetings, 1969-1994 (Box 101A)
  - ACA - Rungius Paintings Information, 1973-1993 (Box 102A)
  - ACA Minutes, 1958-1971; Three Bound Volumes. (Box 108A)
  - ACA Board Meeting Agendas, 1986-2005 (Box 109)
  - ACA Minutes, 1958-2004 (Box 110)
  - ACA Minutes, 1958-2004 (Box 111)
  - ACA Executive Memos, 1979-2003 (Box 112)
- William H. Whyte - Cluster Development, 4
  - Cluster Development - Orders: Paid Invoices 00001-00999 (Box 35)
  - Cluster Development - Orders: Paid Invoices 01000-01999 (Box 36)
  - Cluster Development - Orders: Paid Invoices 02000-02999 (Box 37)
  - Cluster Development - Orders: Paid Invoices 03000-03999 (Box 38)
  - Cluster Development - Orders: Paid Invoices 04000-04999 (Box 39)
  - Cluster Development - Orders: Paid Invoices 05000-05999 (Box 40)
  - Cluster Development - Orders: Paid Invoices 06000-07299 (Box 41)
  - Cluster Development - Orders: Paid Invoices 07300-08899 (Box 42)
  - Citizen's Committee for the ORC Report (CORC) - A-L, Articles and By-laws, Legal (Box 43)
  - Citizen's Committee for the ORC Report (CORC) - M-N (Box 43)
  - Citizen's Committee for the ORC Report (CORC) - O-Z (Box 43)
  - CORC - Articles (Box 43)
  - CORC - Board of Managers (Box 43)
  - CORC - Booklet - Distribution (Box 43)
  - CORC - California Park Bond Issue, 2 folders. (Box 43)
  - CORC - Certificate of Authority, Washington D.C. (Rights to conduct affairs in D.C.) Citizen's Committee (Box 43)
  - CORC - D.C. Workmen's Compensation Act (Box 43)
  - CORC - Charitable Solicitations Act (Washington D.C. for Citizen's Committee) (Box 43)
  - CORC - Chorley., Kenneth (Box 43)
  - CORC - Clippings (Box 43)
  - CORC - Connecticut (Box 43)
  - CORC - Conservation Films (Box 43)
  - CORC - Contributions - Miscellaneous Contributions (Box 43)
  - CORC - Corporate Papers (Box 43)
  - CORC - Dr. Samuel T. DanaStudyre:FutureofCORC (Box 43)
  - CORC - Diamond, Henry L. Memos (Box 43)
  - CORC - Digest (Box 43)
  - CORC - Duddleson, William J. (Box 43)
  - CORC - Ellerkman, Mrs. Hildegard (Box 44)
  - CORC - Employees (Box 44)
  - CORC - Federal Conservation Bills (Box 44)
  - CORC - Federal Conservation Bills - Land and Water, 3 folders. (Box 44)
  - CORC - Federal Conservation Bills - Clippings (Box 44)
  - CORC - Federal Conservation Bills - Reports (Box 44)
  - CORC - Federal Conservation Bills - LSR Letters, 1964 June-July (Box 44)
  - CORC - Federal Conservation Bills - LSR Letters - General Correspondence, 1964 June-July (Box 44)
  - CORC - Finance Committeee - Fund Solicitation (Box 44)
  - CORC - Finances/Financial (Box 44)
  - CORC - Florida Bond Issue (Box 44)
  - CORC - Gregg, Frank (Box 44)
  - CORC - League of Women's Voters' - Education Fund Adult Education Program & Seminar (Box 44)
  - CORC - Massachusetts (Box 44)
  - CORC - Membership Committee (Box 44)
  - CORC - Memoranda (Box 44)
  - CORC - Minutes/Meetings (Box 45)
  - CORC - Minutes/Meetings, 1963 May 21 (Box 45)
  - CORC - Minutes/Meetings, 1963 April 19 (Box 45)
  - CORC - Minutes/Meetings, 1963 April 21 (Box 45)
  - CORC - Minutes/Meetings, 1963 January 31 (Box 45)
  - CORC - Minutes/Meetings, 1962 November 14 (Box 45)
  - CORC - National Association of Counties (Box 45)
  - CORC - Pennsylvania (Box 45)
  - CORC - Printed Material (Box 45)
  - CORC - Procedures (Box 45)
  - CORC - Progress Reports (Box 45)
  - CORC - Public Affairs (Box 45)
  - CORC - LSR (General Files) (Box 45)
  - CORC - Smith, Fred (Box 45)
  - CORC - Study of Resort Industry (Box 45)
  - CORC - Tax Exemptions (Sales and Income and Franchise for Citizen's Committee) - Washington D.C. (Box 45)
  - CORC - Virginia (Box 45)
  - CORC - Whyte, William H. (Box 45)
  - CORC - Work Material (Box 45)
  - CORC - Commission Report, 1963 January-February (Box 46)
  - CORC - Commission Report, 1963 March-April (Box 46)
  - CORC - Commission Report, 1963 May (Box 46)
  - CORC - Book Material (Box 46)
  - Distribution of CORC Study Reports (Box 46)
  - Leather Bound Study Reports (Box 46)
  - American Conservation Association (Box 47)
  - Whyte, William Correspondence, A-Z, 7 folders. (Box 47)
  - Correspondence Files, 1961-1966; 4 folders. (Box 47)
  - England Conference, 1965 (Box 48)
  - Follow-Up Conferences (Box 48)
  - Ford Foundation Committee (Box 48)
  - Garden Club Talks (Box 48)
  - Long Island Meeting, 1965 October 20 (Box 48)
  - Michigan Conference, 1965 October 12 (Box 48)
  - Open Space Action Committee, 2 folders (Box 48)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1966 November 10 (Box 48)
  - Sierra Club Critique (Box 48)
  - Task Force Arrangements Report (Box 48)
  - Virginia Conference, 1965 December 9 (Box 48)
  - YMCA Conference, 1966 July (Box 48)
  - Conservation Foundation, 2 folders. (Box 49)
  - Conservation Foundation (Ford Proposal) (Box 49)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Whyte WMH - General (Box 49)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Whyte WMH - Act (Box 49)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Whyte WMH - Beautification Grant (Box 49)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Whyte WMH - Compact Matters (Box 49)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Whyte WMH - Con Edison (Box 49)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Whyte WMH - Georgia Pacific Plan (Box 49)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Whyte WMH - Goals Memo (Box 49)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Whyte WMH - Land Acquisition Proposal (Box 49)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Whyte WMH - Minutes (Box 49)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Whyte WMH - Newsletters (Box 49)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Whyte WMH - Planning Committee (Box 49)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Whyte WMH - Project Review (Box 49)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission: Whyte WMH - Report - Reactions (Box 49)
  - California - American River Parkway (Box 50)
  - California Bond Issue (Box 50)
  - California (1963 Bond Issue) (Box 50)
  - California - Department of Natural Resources (Box 50)
  - California Legislature: Fred Parr, Lipman (Box 50)
  - California, Loomis Valley (Box 50)
  - California, Los Angeles County (Box 50)
  - California, Monterey County - Carmel Valley (Box 50)
  - California, Monterrey County - Clippings, 1961 (Box 50)
  - California, Monterrey County - Scenic Reserve (Box 50)
  - California, Palo Alto (Box 50)
  - California, San Diego (Box 50)
  - California, San Mateo County (Box 50)
  - California, San Mateo County - Golf Club Situation (Box 50)
  - California, Santa Barbara (Box 50)
  - California, Santa Clara County (Box 50)
  - California, Sutter County (Box 50)
  - California, University of California Site Study (Box 50)
  - California, Sam Wood Connecticut (Box 50)
  - Connecticut - A Proposal for Action (Box 50)
  - Connecticut - Open Space Action (Box 50)
  - Florida (Box 50)
  - Illinois (Box 50)
  - Illinois - Open Space Committee (Box 50)
  - Illinois - Winnebago County (Box 50)
  - Illinois - Marion Connty Met Department (Box 50)
  - Iowa Conservation Boards - Baltimore County (Box 50)
  - Baltimore County (IA) (Box 50)
  - Michigan (Box 50)
  - Minnesota (Box 50)
  - Minnesota - St. Paul (Box 50)
  - Minnesota - Northfield (Box 50)
  - University of Missouri Prairie Preserve (Box 50)
  - Bolack; New Mexico (Box 50)
  - New York State Highway Legislation (Box 50)
  - Ohio - Dayton (Box 50)
  - Ohio - Glen Helen (Box 50)
  - Ohio - Indian Hill (Box 50)
  - Ohio Turnpike Comm. (Box 50)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 50)
  - Puerto Rico - San Juan (Box 50)
  - Texas (Box 50)
  - Wisconsin Campaign for Resource Program (Box 50)
  - Wisconsin - Highway Legislation (Box 50)
  - Wisconsin - Gaylord Nelson (Box 50)
  - Wisconsin: The Program 62, 1962 (Box 50)
  - Town Houses - City - Capitol Park, Washington, D.C. (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - Colonial Park, Louisville, Kentucky (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - Cross Keys, Baltimore, Maryland (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - Dudley Square, Shreveport, LA (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - East Hills, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - Fairway Gardens, New Haven, CT (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - Geneva Terrace, San Francisco (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - Georgetown (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - Hartshorn, Richmond, Virginia (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - Huntington Continental, Huntington Beach (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - Liberty Square, New Haven, CT (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - Morrell Park, Far Northeast, Philadelphia, PA (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - Park Towne, St. Louis, MO (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - River Park, Washington D.C. (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - Quinnipiac Gardens, New Haven, CT (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - University News, Philadelphia, PA (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - City - Vista Bahia, Newport Beach (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - Suburban - Creekside North, Walnut Creek (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - Suburban - Georgetown South, Manassas, VA (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - Suburban - Heather Hills, Louisville, KY (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - Suburban - Pomeroy Green, Santa Clara, CA (Box 51)
  - Town Houses - Suburban - Terrace at Peacock Gap, Marin Bay, CA (Box 51)
  - Detached House Clusters - Brunswick Acres, South Brunswick, NJ (Box 51)
  - Detached House Clusters - Georgetown East, Cedarburg, WI (Box 51)
  - Detached House Clusters - Hampden Heights, Denver, CO (Box 51)
  - Detached House Clusters - The Highlands, Ledyard, CT (Box 51)
  - Detached House Clusters - Lakeside Hills, St. Louis, MO (Box 51)
  - Detached House Clusters - Parkwood, Lowes Grove, NC (Box 51)
  - Detached House Clusters - Sunrise, Guilford, CT (Box 51)
  - Detached House Clusters - Village Green, Hillsborough, NJ (Box 51)
  - Detached House Clusters - Ville du Pare, Meguon, WI (Box 51)
  - Detached House Clusters - The Woodlands, Farmington, CT (Box 51)
  - Super Developments - Americana Fairfax, Fairfax County, VA (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - Carmel Valley Golf and Country Club, Carmel (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - Chapel Hill, Atlanta GA (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - Crofton, Baltimore, MD (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - El Dorado Hills, Sacramento, CA (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - Four Seasons, St. Louis, MO (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - Greenhaven '70, Sacramento, CA (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - Hunting Creek, Louisville, KY (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - Lakehurst, (Columbine Community) Denver, CO (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - Loma Vista, Kansas City, MO (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - New Seabury, Cape Cod, MA (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - Reston, Fairfax County, VA (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - Sea Pines Plantation, Hilton Head, SC (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - Skyline Forest, Monterey, CA (Box 52)
  - Super Developments - Westchester, Springfield, IL (Box 52)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - College Green, Fullerton, CA (Box 52)
    Cited but not logged in report
  - Miscellaneous Developments - St. Mary's Close, Shincliffe, England (Box 52)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Society Hill, Philadelphia, PA (Box 52)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Starwood, Aspen, CO (Box 52)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Sunnyside Gardens & Badburn (Box 52)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Williamsburg Square, Phoenix, AZ (Box 52)
  - Biographical with Developments - Belser, Karl - Santa Clara County, CA (Box 52)
  - Biographical with Developments - Blankman, Norman - Old Westbury & Tenafly, NY (Box 52)
  - Biographical with Developments - Caitlin, Robert- Rockaway, NJ (Box 52)
  - Biographical with Developments - Clay, Grady (Box 52)
  - Biographical with Developments - Freels, Larry - Rheem, Terrace, Lawrence Square, Creekside (Box 52)
  - Biographical with Developments - Gruen, Victor (Box 52)
  - Biographical with Developments - Lloyd, Gerald (Box 52)
  - Biographical with Developments - Nelson, William (Box 52)
  - Biographical with Developments - Rahenkamp, John - Pitney Estates (Box 52)
  - Biographical with Developments - Roach, William Sommerset County, NJ (Box 52)
  - Biographical with Developments - Edward Stone House (Box 52)
  - Biographical with Developments - Syracuse, Lee, CT (Box 52)
  - Originals of Appendix - Appendix A- galleys returned by developers (Box 52)
  - Originals of Appendix - Appendix B & C- Planned Unit Development (Box 52)
  - Originals of Appendix - Appendix D- Home Owners Association Index (Box 52)
  - Originals of Appendix - Index (Box 52)
  - Originals of Appendix - Cluster- Critiques (Box 52)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Apple Hill, St. Louis, MO (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Arbor Park and Oxmoor, Louisville, KY (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Baldwin Hills (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Cincinnati: Hamilton County Storm Drainage Plan (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Conantum, Concord, Mass. & other Carl Koch projects (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Crystal Shores, Lake Tahoe (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Fremont, CA (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Green Manor, Manchester, CT (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Guilford Terraces, CT (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Hanover East and Peachtree Estates, Atlanta, GA (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Indian Lake, Somerset, PA & Indian Creek, Merion, PA (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Irvine Ranch, Pereira (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Kansas City (Box 53)
    Miscellaneous good plans by Hare and Hare all defeated
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Monterey Penninsula (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Mosby Woods, VA and other D.C., Maryland and Virginia (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - New Castle, DE (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - North Lake Plan, WI (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Parkside Estates, Fresno, CA (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Parkwood, San Jose, CA (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - St. Louis, MO: Community Unit Development (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - St. Louis, MO: Pierremont & Bellerive Estates (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous Developments - Washington Heights, FL (Box 53)
  - Cluster Study - Subject Files - General Correspondence (Box 53)
  - Cluster Study - Subject Files - Condominium Financing (Box 53)
  - Cluster Study - Subject Files - Density Zoning: Planned Unit Development (Box 53)
  - Cluster Study - Subject Files - FHA Glossary of terms (Box 53)
  - Cluster Study - Subject Files - Gas Lamps (Box 53)
  - Cluster Study - Subject Files - Home Owners Association Forms (Box 53)
  - Cluster Study - Subject Files - Legal (Box 53)
  - Cluster Study - Subject Files - Miscellaneous Clippings (Box 53)
  - Cluster Study - Subject Files - Propaganda (Box 53)
  - Cluster Study - Subject Files - Cluster Zoning Ordinances (Box 53)
  - Chapters - Forward (Box 53)
  - Chapters - Economics (Box 53)
  - Chapters - Community Attitude (Box 53)
  - Chapters - The Marketplace (Box 53)
  - Chapters - Legal (Box 53)
  - Chapters - Homeowners Associations (Box 53)
  - Chapters - Town House (Box 53)
  - Chapters - Super Development (Box 53)
  - Chapters - Linkage (Box 53)
  - Chapters - Kinds of Spaces (Box 53)
  - Chapters - Captions (Box 53)
  - The Report - Promotion - Conference (Box 54)
  - The Report - Copyright Certificate "Cluster Development" (Box 54)
  - The Report - Flyer (Box 54)
  - The Report - Media-TV (Box 54)
  - The Report - Distribution (Box 54)
  - The Report - Magazines (Box 54)
  - The Report - Newspapers (Box 54)